OK. Did Cavett say we would have any essay questions?
好了.Cavett有说我们会有问答题吗?
No. Just multiple choice.
没有.只有多选题.
We must be done.
那我们一定复习完了.
We must be.
一定是.
I can't think of anything else to study.
我真想不出再学什么了.
-Great.  -Great.
-太好了. -太好了.
So the question is...
现在的问题是...
should I have a big party for my birthday?
我过生日要不要搞一个大派对?
Absolutely. Can I wear your red dress?
绝对的.我能穿你的红裙子吗?
Justine. The party may not even happen
Justine.派对还不一定开呢
and you already want to wear my clothes.
你就想穿我的衣服了.
But I look so good in that dress.
可是我穿那条红裙子真的很漂亮.
Where is it?
它在哪儿?
Here it is.
在这呢.
Anyway, my parents would like to throw a party for me.
不管怎样,我父母想为我举办一个派对.
Uh huh?
I don't know. Do you think it's stupid?
我拿不定主意.你认为这是不是很傻?
Sweet sixteen?
甜蜜16岁派对?
Oh yeah. Sweet sixteen.
Oh 是的.甜蜜16岁.
Well, you don't have to wear a sign or anything.
Well,你不需要挂个牌子或什么的.
Yeah. We don't have to call it a sweet sixteen party.
对.我们没必要把它称为甜蜜16岁派对.
Try it with a necklace.
配上项链试试.
I like it with the necklace.
我喜欢它配着项链.
That tea party your mom did was great.
你妈妈办的那个茶会挺棒的.
Yeah, it could be really nice.
对.确实可能会很不错.
On the other hand, a bunch of us could just go out.
不过另一方面,我们几个人也可以出去庆祝.
That would be fun, too.
那也会很有意思.
Beth, your birthday's not for a few months, right?
Beth,你的生日还有几个月吧?
Six weeks.
还有六个星期.
So you have time to decide.
你还有时间来做决定.
You never wear this. I'm taking it. OK?
你从不穿这衣服.我要拿走它.行吗?
OK. Are you hungry?
行.你饿了吗?
I could eat.
我可以吃一点.
So could I. Let's do it.
我也是.咱们去吃饭吧.